<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pradyumn Goel&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pradyumn Goel&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 17:12:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Started Playing Dragonblox Ultimate</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/started-playing-dragonblox-ultimate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 17:12:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/started-playing-dragonblox-ultimate/</guid>
      <description>Well I got bored of YBA and wanted to play something else. Then I found this game called Dragonblox Ultimate. It&amp;rsquo;s a very good game and is exactly the type of games which I find most fun. Grinding games.
It&amp;rsquo;s like a simulator. With stats and everything. On the first day itself I got like 50,00 stats and SSJ2 Form. I am currently aiming for Majin SSJ. As my side is evil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still Not Getting Hermit Purple and Bedwars 100 Player mode</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/still-not-getting-hermit-purple-and-bedwars-100-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 17:38:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/still-not-getting-hermit-purple-and-bedwars-100-player/</guid>
      <description>Well I just tried getting hermit purple through rokas and arrows&amp;hellip; again. Instead when all my rokas finished. I got airsmith. Which is like such a bad stand. I don&amp;rsquo;t think this game will ever give me hermit purple. But I have to keep trying.
Also today I played Roblox Bedwars with my friends. There is this new gamemode (which was there earlier but got removed) called 100 player mode. It&amp;rsquo;s like 24 teams, some colors are same, but the same colors are like some are aplha some are beta some are charlie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Got Tusk Act 3 and Roka&#39;d D4C</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/just-got-tusk-act-3-and-rokad-d4c/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 18:39:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/just-got-tusk-act-3-and-rokad-d4c/</guid>
      <description>Hello Everybody I&amp;rsquo;m jus here to inform you that I decided to get Tusk Act 4 and currently have Tusk Act 3. Also, I let go of D4C and I just got Silver Chariot Requim&amp;hellip; Although I really want hermit purple.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why people are so crazy about shiny stands. I mean people want six pistols shiny&amp;hellip; Six pistols is the worst stand in the game&amp;hellip; And just because the shiny looks good they want it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year&#39;s Eve Gaming</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/newyearsevepost/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 15:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/newyearsevepost/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s New Year&amp;rsquo;s Gaming was EPIC. I just got prestige 2 :D. Im going to get some levels and just spam sbr (Steel Ball Run)
I think that since my stand storage is open Im gonna get sptw coz I need a melee stand too.
I know a great sbr strategy with d4c&amp;hellip; Its to dimension hop ALL THE TIME. Especially in the PvP section. As to get away from all the wipers for a good amount of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid Shooter, An easy to play game in which you have to dodge and blast asteroids!</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/asteroidshooter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 18:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/asteroidshooter/</guid>
      <description>This is a game in which you must dodge asteroids and blast them using your bullets, you dont have unlimited bullets and need to collect bullet backages.
To test it out, visit here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letter Arranger, my first game in javascript</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/letterarranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 18:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/letterarranger/</guid>
      <description>This is a simple game in which you have to order a generated set of alphabets in alphabetical order
To test it out, visit here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Republic day special, A project I made for India&#39;s republic day</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/republicdayspecial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 18:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/republicdayspecial/</guid>
      <description>This is a project I made to celebrate India&amp;rsquo;s republic day
To check it out, visit here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Jumper, A chrome dino game based game</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/schooljumper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 18:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/schooljumper/</guid>
      <description>This is a game in which you must jump in time to avoid failing in school exams, you get bombs every few seconds and start off with 3 bombs. Use them wisely ;)
To test it out, visit here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Glitch</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/theglitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 18:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/theglitch/</guid>
      <description>A story about a universal glitch&amp;hellip;
To check it out, visit here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Prestige 1 YBA</title>
      <link>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/gettingpres1yba/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 17:39:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pradyumngoel.com/posts/gettingpres1yba/</guid>
      <description>I just prestiged from pres 0 to pres 1 Yo I just got prestige 1 in YBA Roblox and I can now enter colloseum :D
I can do 2v2 and 1v1
I also completed the storyline and am rn lvl 30
My plan to get pres 2 is: Dopey quest until lvl 35 =&amp;gt; Dio quest until lvl 40 =&amp;gt; prestige
Well my current stats are =&amp;gt;
Stand: d4c
Prestige: 1</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
